《德古拉》剧情回顾
Previously on Dracula...
我不需要你的开价
I do not need to see your offer.
我对出售没有兴趣
My interests are not for sale.
无论多少价钱
At any price.
Grayson先生让我去他的公司上班
Mr. Grayson has offered me a position in his firm.
我要你告诉我
I want you to tell me
关于Laurent大人的一切
everything you know about Lord Laurent.
你想知道的所有事情
Everything you need to know you can find out
今晚10点钟  都在斯温伯恩俱乐部
10:00 p.M. At the Swinburne Club.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
我相信你不会对我调用先知有何异议吧
I presume you have no objection to my deployment of the seers.
伦敦有个吸血鬼
There is a vampire in London.
你们要立刻找到他
You shall find him forthwith.
他发现了他们
He detected them and then employed
然后采取某种策略
some kind of countermeasure.
我会追击并摧毁他
I will track him, and I will destroy him.
为什么让Harker把那个女人带到您身边？
Why engage Harker to bring the woman into your orbit?
无疑您自己就可以轻而易举得到她
Surely you have the power to simply take her.
把她变的和我一样
To turn her into as such as I am,
那会令人憎恶的
it would be an abomination.
—— 真 爱 字 幕 组 ——
出  品
翻译：老马  安静  飞越无限
校对：幸福ing形式
组长：凡凡
后期：飞越无限
监制：幸福ing形式
本字幕纯属学习交流
招贤纳士：QQ群233183580
====原创翻译  转载标明====
====如有翻译疏忽  还请指正原谅====
====祝大家观影愉快====
既然命中注定  那就遵循而行
So it is written, and so it shall be done.
Ilona
Ilona.
我在哪？
Where am I?
为什么我没死？
Why am I not dead?
这就是你反抗的价值
This is the price of your defiance.
用你反抗上帝的力量
Using the power of the God you denounced,
恶龙会创造了一个怪物
Ordo Draco has made a monster.
汝命注定  被判永远在黑暗中徘徊
Thou art condemned, condemned to endless night.
呀！
Yah!
Vlad Tepes被判为不死之身
Vlad Tepes is condemned to be undead.
我还不知道您会弹钢琴  先生
I had no idea you played, sir.
已经有一个多世纪没有摸过琴键了
It's been over a century since I last put fingers to keys.
我在想Jayne Wetherty女士
I was thinking about Lady Jayne Wetherby
还有她明显的不良嗜好
and her decidedly unwholesome avocation.
您说哪个  先生？
Really? Which one, sir?
当然是她猎鬼爱好
Her vampire hunting, of course.
很难去相信
It stretches credulity
她与恶龙会没有任何关系
to think she's unaffiliated with the Order.
我也同意  先生
I would tend to agree, sir.
但是她是一介妇人
But then she is a female.
不论如何
I suppose I shall have to ascertain it
我觉得我应该查明这事儿
one way or the other.
那是什么？
What's that?
那个是书面证明
Ah, yes, written confirmation
来自Laurent大人的律师
from Lord Laurent's solicitor.
恭喜您  先生
Congratulations, sir.
您现在是大英冷剂公司的主要控股人了
You are now a majority stockholder of British Imperial Coolant.
—— 德 古 拉 ——
第一季第三集
Jonathan  哦
Jonathan. Oh.
早上好  你精神不太好啊
Good morning. You look dreadful.
收拾好行李  我们该走了
Pack your trunk and we shall go.
去哪？
Go where?
母亲去巴黎了  把我一个人扔在这
Mother decamped for Paris and left me on my own,
你也知道我多讨厌独自生活
and you know how much I hate that.
所以如果药剂能同时解救我的寂寞
So, if the cure for my loneliness and your broken heart
还有你伤透了的心的话...
are the same thing...
你怎么知道的？
How did you know?
我亲爱的Mina
Dearest Mina,
不要为Jonathan Harker落一点泪
do not shed a single tear for Jonathan Harker.
实话说  这毫无意义
Honestly, there's no point in wasting a single minute more
别浪费时间去想他变得那混蛋样了
thinking about what an awful twit he turned out to be.
现在你应该和我一起找点乐子
Not when you could be having fun with me instead.
Murray医生  我手下有两个亲戚
Dr. Murray, I have two young relatives
聪明伶俐的年轻人
under my charge, sharp, young minds,
但最近他们的精神状态有点儿问题
but lately they've experienced a great, psychic strain.
我知道  以您在这里的能力
I understand, in your capacity as director of this institution,
您一定曾治疗过
that you've had the privilege of serving as an alienist
很多上流名士吧
to certain individuals of high renown.
我确实治疗过一些公众人士了
I have treated a number of public figures.
当然您应理解  我不能泄露…
You understand of course that I can't divulge...
不不不  您的谨慎是众所周知的
No, no, your reputation for discretion precedes you.
这也正是我来的原因
Which is why I'm here.
当然不是为我自己
Not for myself naturally,
是为了我的亲人
but for close relations
希望能匿名会诊
who wish to remain anonymous.
那么  需要我怎样帮您？
Please, how may I be of service?
大英冷剂公司
你应该确保我们的订单
You should be able to meet our order
没有任何问题  Worth先生
without a problem, Mr. Worth.
你的意思是  要我们把整个运营
Are you suggesting we dedicate the entirety of our operation
都只为一个客户而服务吗？
to the needs of a single client?
不不
No.
但是我觉得他是这样想的
But I think he is.
你们两个  滚出我的办公室  现在！
Get out of my office now, both of you.
很好  不过我很遗憾的
Very well. Though I must regretfully
通知你  你被解雇了
inform you that your employment here is terminated,
即刻生效
effective immediately.
你没有权力解聘我
You don't have the authority to dismiss me.
你除了是个有钱人的狗腿还是什么
You're nothing more than a rich man's novelty
我甚至不会让你进我家的门
I wouldn't even let into my home.
稍等一下  你没有权力
Now hold on a minute. You have no right
- 这么说…  - 作为大英冷剂公司的
- to speak... - As a majority shareholder
主要控股人
of British Imperial Lubrication and Coolant Co., limited,
Alexander Grayson现在是你的老板
Alexander Grayson is now your employer.
所以我说时  我就拥有他的权力
When I speak, I speak with his authority.
我再给你一次机会  照我说的做
I'll give you a second chance to do as you're told.
我说的够清楚了吗？
Have I made myself clear?
是的
Yes.
先生
Sir.
希望将来你能对得起Grayson先生
In future I'd appreciate it if you tried to earn
对你的信任和慷慨
Mr. Grayson's trust, not to mention generosity,
首先要做到的就是在商务洽谈的时候
and I'd start by sharing your undivided attention
一心一意
during business meetings.
对不起  是我没有做好
I'm sorry. There's no excuse.
我给你一份名单
I provided a list of individuals
Grayson先生非常希望你和他们
Mr. Grayson would very much like you
缔结友谊
to foster friendships with.
我确信名单上大部分人你都认识
I'm sure you recognize most of the names on the list.
还有  Harker
And, Harker...
再也不要在任何人面前  自作主张为我说话
Never again presume to defend me to anyone.
你愿意的话  我可以合成一种兴奋剂
If you wish, I'd be happy to mix a stimulant.
现在可以告诉我  你的客户名了吗？
Now may I inquire as to your client's name?
我觉得不便透漏
I'd rather not say.
哦  医生  又不是什么学术秘密
Please, doctor, indulge a humble academic.
那么  教授  我可以
Well, professor, I suppose I can rely
信任你吧？
on your discretion?
是Jayne Wetherby女士
She is Lady Jayne Wetherby.
啊
Ah.
我懂了  懂了
I see. I see.
我们的猎人在为她的先知寻找新药
Our huntswoman is seeking a new drug for her seers.
是的
Yes.
我非常确定
I'm certain of it.
把药给她
Give it to her.
嗯  如果你坚持的话  我会做一种
Well, if you insist, I'll concoct a serum
药效不足的血清
of inadequate potency.
好使我们的敌人另寻他法
And force our enemy to seek a new solution elsewhere
让我们无法控制吗
beyond our control.
干的不错啊  Van Helsing
Well done Van Helsing.
目光短浅  愚蠢荒唐
Short-sighted and foolish.
那你有更好的计划吗？
I suppose you have a better plan?
如果Grayson的地磁计划成功实施
If Grayson brings off his geomagnetic scheme,
那恶龙会的石油股份
the Order's oil and petroleum holdings
将会变得一文不值
won't be worth the paper they're written on.
我很清楚他对我们
I am well aware of the threat he poses
所有人的威胁
to all of us.
那你发什么疯
So what on earth possessed you
把你冷剂公司的股份卖给他？
to sell him your shares in British Imperial Coolant?
如果我有别的选择
Had I a choice in the matter,
我永远也不会同意他的条件
I never would have agreed to his terms.
他威胁你了
He threatened you.
对于违背誓言的兄弟
There is no protection, none,
是不会提供一丁点保护的
for any brother who violates the principal oath.
如果你想为自己辩护什么的话
If you have anything to say to me in your defense,
我建议你现在就说  否则就站在兄弟们面前
I suggest you do so now or stand before your brothers
接受应有的惩罚
and suffer the punishment proscribed.
杀了我
Kill me.
求你 杀了我吧
Please. Kill me.
嘘
Shh.
Grayson
Grayson.
这边请
This way, please.
到了  女士
Here we are. Madam.
Daniel  那是Alexander Grayson的人吗？
Daniel, is that Alexander Grayson's man?
Jonathan Harker
Jonathan Harker.
是的  父亲  是他
Yes, father, that's him.
Winston
Winston.
送瓶波尔多葡萄酒给那位年轻人
Will you send a bottle of Bordeaux over to that young man
独自用餐的那位  Harker先生
dining on his own, Mr. Harker,
以表心意
with our compliments?
有问题吗？
Is there a problem?
没问题  先生  只是Harker先生派我们
No, sir. It's just Mr. Harker directed us
把这个送给您  一点儿心意
to send this over with his compliments.
1890年的拉图
Hmm, Latour 1890.
我们应该好好转转
We shall make a full circuit,
从萨沃伊开始
starting at the Savoy
然后晚点到达官员俱乐部舞会
and arriving fashionably late at the officers' club ball,
那儿的男人肯定仪表堂堂  即使有点过于彬彬有礼
where the men shall be delicious, if a little too well-behaved.
Lucy...  你来的时候
Lucy... When you went to the house,
你确定没看见Jonathan吗？
are you sure you didn't see Jonathan?
没有  Mina
No, Mina.
一张便条  一张卡片都没见  什么也没有
Not a note, not a card, nothing.
显然他已经找到了适合他的蠢娘们
No doubt he's already found some silly little cow
当他所谓的“得体的英国妻子”
who fits his description of a proper English wife.
我们该怎么对那些可心的官员们呢？
What do we do with these delicious officers?
女士们
Ladies.
詹姆斯旅馆
你要去哪儿？
Where are you going?
你知道的  我得走了
You know I have to.
像个夜贼一样偷偷溜走吗？
To steal away like a thief in the night?
木已成舟
The die is cast.
那我们逃吧
Then we'll run away.
逃得远远的  逃离恶龙社
We'll run as far and as fast as we can
逃到没有它束缚和法规的地方去
to a safe haven beyond the reach of the Order.
没有这样的地方  Daniel
There's no such place, Daniel.
你知道的
And you know it.
-那我们就坦承一切  -你疯了吗？
- Then we'll simply come clean. - Are you mad?
我的名声怎么办？
What of my reputation?
我可不愿为了苟活于世
I will not shirk death
而让我的家族蒙羞
only to see my family's legacy compromised.
在我向那个美国人屈从的时候
I signed my death warrant
我已将生死置之度外
the moment that I capitulated to that American.
我早就清楚会发生什么
I knew this when I did it.
再一次  我还会这样做的
And I would do it again.
停！
Stop!
终于等来了
Finally.
我们已经等了一整晚了
We've been waiting here all night.
先生  太阳出来了
Sir, the sun.
再等会儿
Just a moment more.
什么东西
What is it?
先生
Sir.
我想看见
I want to see her face
她读卡片时的表情
when she reads the card.
是Jonathan写给你的吗？
Are they from Jonathan?
-不是  -让我看看
- No. - Oh, let me see.
很抱歉  先生
I'm sorry, sir.
该死！
Damn!
“面对梦想  人人都可能会踟躇
"When it comes to dreams, one might falter,
但只要不放弃就不算失败
"But the only way to fail is to abandon them.
恭贺”
Congratulations."
没署名
It's unsigned.
你觉得会是谁送的
Who do you think might have sent them?
我不知道
I haven't the slightest.
好吧
Okay.
你的免疫阳光研究有进展没？
Have you made any progress with the solar vaccine?
因为正在为Jayne女士研究血清  所以没有
Not while devising the serum for Lady Jayne, no.
我还得在黑暗中躲藏多久？
How long must I spend skulking in the shadows?
我想像常人一样在阳光下行走
I want to walk in the sun like any other man.
你永远不可能和常人一样
You will never be like any other man.
你给我记好了
You would do well to remember that.
我把见光时间延长到了
I've increased the duration of the vaccine
三分钟十二秒
to three minutes and 12 seconds.
阿
Ah!
- 三分钟  - 零十二秒
- Three minutes. - And 12 seconds.
你只给我留了在灰飞烟灭前
You leave me just enough time to have a cup of tea
喝杯茶的时间啊
before I burst into flames.
Stephen James Laurent兄弟
Brother Stephen James Laurent,
你有把个人利益置于
did you place your own interests before those
令人敬畏的秩序之上吗？
of this most august order?
有
I did.
惩罚已在这里尽数列出
The punishment is proscribed within these pages.
如之所书
So it is written...
履之如规
And so it shall be done.
这些规矩是
The sentence has been handed down
代代相传
from generation to generation.
你甘愿接受刀刑吗？
Will you accept the blade?
我愿意
I will.
我想我懂自己的感觉
I think I know how I feel.
我只为你付出
I only pay it for you
你该将我捧在手心
You should be picking me up
你却将我抛在地上
Instead you're dragging me down
你在我头顶飞翔
You flying over my head.
降落在了镇子的每个角落
You're landing all over town.
想什么呢？
What are you thinking?
你…  你该再喝点苦艾酒
Ah, you... You need more absinthe.
或许吧  但是通过研究实验
Perhaps, but by way of careful study and experiment,
我已经知道我的酒量了
I may have discovered my limit.
才貌兼备啊
Beautiful and witty.
我不知道是该为你写首诗
Hmm, I'm not sure whether to write a poem
还是画幅画像呢
or paint your portrait.
我在想  你用纸张和花言巧语奉承过
I wonder, how many women have you flattered with paper
多少女人呢？
and canvass?
你是最后一个  我保证
You're the last one. I promise.
我是通过一个有限孔径
My way of contact with reality
来和现实接触的
is through a limited aperture.
我们之间的际遇会在那个小孔里…
Our transfluence takes place through one small...
发生
opening.
很好笑吗？
I amuse you?
女人们有为之倾倒的吗？
Do women really fall for that?
“际遇”
"Transfluence."
你如此出众
How superior you are.
像你这样的女人
A woman of your means
来到低下的地方猎奇
slumming the lower depths.
就像观察动物园的人一样观察着我们
Observing us like we're animals at the zoo.
啊
Ah.
可这里没有栅栏
You see there are no bars here.
我们也没有被关在笼子里
And we are not caged.
好了  我很好
All right. I'm fine. Fine.
滚！
Move!
Grayson先生
Mr. Grayson.
谢谢你救我
Thank you for my rescue.
不算什么
It was nothing.
但你来这做什么？
But what brought you here?
这地方的派对众所周知
This place is notorious for its parties.
我喜欢那的音乐
I like the music.
嗯
Hmm.
你有心事
You're troubled.
- 没有  - 告诉我
- No. - Tell me.
拜托
Please.
是和Jonathan的事
It's Jonathan.
Harker吗？
Harker?
我不相信他会做任何伤害你的事
I can't believe he'd do anything to hurt you.
但他做了
But he did.
他对我说很不好的话  我就离开了
He said the most horrible things, and I walked away,
那以后我们再也没见过面
and we haven't seen each other since.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know how to fix it.
（波西米亚夜生活：代表放纵）
波西米亚式的夜生活勉强算是快乐的替代品
You know, bohemian nightlife is a poor substitute for happiness.
有时我们命中注定的人和地方
Sometimes the people and places we are meant for
会使我们惊讶难耐
take us by surprise.
这上演着戏剧呢
Well, there's a tableau vivant.
犹如沼泽里的Heathcliff和Cathy
Heathcliff and Cathy on the moors.
（出自《呼啸山庄》）
天色已晚
It's getting late.
-我可以送你们俩回家吗  -不用  谢谢
- May I see you ladies home? - No. Thank you.
我们的马车在外面等着呢
Our carriage is waiting.
晚安  Murray小姐  Westenra小姐
Miss Murray, Miss Westenra.
谢谢  Grayson先生
Thank you... Mr. Grayson.
昨天我和你名单上列出的一些人共进午餐
I had lunch with several of the men on your list yesterday...
Davenport先生和他的儿子
Davenport and son,
Rothcroft大人  Shaw上将
Lord Rothcroft, General Shaw.
我知道了  还有谁？
I see. Anyone else?
Browning先生
A Mr. Browning.
-Browning？  -没错  他也参加了你的派对
- Browning? - Yes, he was at your party.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
非常确定
Yes, quite.
一个我们共同的朋友
Now a mutual friend has told me
秘密地告诉我
in complete discretion of course
最近你和一位年轻女士闹矛盾了
that you have recently broken from a young lady.
我忘了她的名字了
Her name escapes me.
Mina Murray.
多迷人的姑娘
Charming gal.
如果你不介意的话  我不想讨论这件事
I'd rather not discuss it, if you don't mind.
可我介意
But I do.
我只是防止你把我的书房
If only to prevent you from turning my study
变成殡仪馆
into a funeral parlor.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我认识Murray小姐
I've known Miss Murray...
Mina…很久了
Mina...for a long time.
她一直很倔强
She's always been very stubborn.
就算我打算娶她为妻  共度余生
She insists on continuing her studies despite the fact
她还是坚持要不顾世俗
that I now have the means and every intention
继续她的学业
of supporting her as my wife.
我明白了
I understand.
-你明白了？  - 嗯哼
- You do? - Uh-huh.
我明白了你就是个傻瓜
I understand that you are a fool.
一个想挑战世俗
How can a man who wishes to defy social convention
提升自己的男人
and rise above his station
怎么会用世俗禁锢自己的爱人呢？
deny the same thing in the woman he loves?
你是说我是个伪君子
You're calling me a hypocrite.
不  Harker
No, Harker.
我说你是个傻瓜
I'm calling you a fool.
但你是个恋爱中的男人
But you are a man in love.
恋爱中的男人都这样
And they are very often the same thing.
工作结束了  回家吧
Finish up. Go home.
恩
Mm.
你醒了
You're up.
想事儿呢
Thinking.
哦  “思考啊”
Oh. "Thinking."
我就是想想  你知道的  偶尔想想
I do think, you know, every so often.
那你想什么呢？
And what are you thinking about?
你
You.
你鼓励我…
You inspire me to...
我也不知道怎么说  让我更自立了
I don't know, greater independence, I suppose.
几点了？
What time is it?
两点
2:00.
我们把半天时间赠予了黑夜啊
We gave half the day to the night.
-两点？  - Mina  怎么了？
-2:00? - Mina, what is it?
我错过了Van Helsing教授的课
I missed Professor Van Helsing's class.
薄荷能舒缓胃不适
Peppermint to soothe the stomach,
柳树皮会减轻头痛
willow bark to ease the pounding in your head.
苦口  却是良药
It tastes awful, but it will work wonders.
谢谢  教授
Thank you, professor.
Murray小姐
Miss Murray,
我是在你身上浪费时间吗？
am I wasting my time with you?
有梦想就要有奋斗
There are dreams we must fight for.
如果你想冲出
If you want to advance beyond the boundaries
社会于你的禁锢
society has made for you,
你就要奋斗
you must fight.
您没有浪费您的时间
You're not wasting your time.
再给我一次机会  我会证明给您
Give me a second chance, and I will prove it to you.
明天早上5点整到这里
Return here tomorrow morning at 5:00 a.M. Sharp.
你这个学期要当我的助手
You will report to me as my assistant for the term.
给Jayne夫人那先知的血清已经准备好了
The serum for Lady Jayne's seers is ready.
我们要寻本溯源
We'll track their power to its source,
一场灾难将会降临这座城市
and there will be a plague upon this city.
拿着这个直接到纸上的这个地址
Take this directly to the address as written.
别磨蹭
Don't dawdle.
如果一个小时内你带着签字的交货收据回来
If you return within an hour with a signed receipt of delivery,
就再给你一先令作为奖励
a second shilling will be your reward.
- 去吧 - 好的 先生
- Go on. - Yes, sir.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
兴奋剂起效了吗 妹妹？
Is the stimulant working, sister?
你能看到那个吸血鬼么？
Can you see the vampire?
我能看到  兴奋剂有效果了
I can see. It's working.
那个吸血鬼  他和她在一起
The vampire. He's with her.
救救我
Help me.
我们被人下毒了
We've been poisoned.
我看到我的血清起效了
I see my serum has taken hold.
目前来看  你们都动不了了
By now you will both be paralyzed.
你们知道
Do you have any idea...
听到自己的妻儿的尖叫
what it's like to hear the screams
会是什么样的心情吗？
of your wife and children?
我的孩子要是活到现在也有20岁了
My children would be in their 20s now.
就是因为惩罚我的不屈服
The Order burned them alive for no other reason
恶龙会就活活的烧死了他们
than to punish me for my disobedience.
我失去了一切
I lost everything.
你们在找的那个怪物
The monster you seek,
我不能让你们找到他
I cannot let you find him.
直到我们一劳永逸地摧毁了恶龙会
Not as long as he is of use to me.
他对我都会很有用
Until we've destroyed the Order once and for all.
我担心你们死后
I'm afraid traces of the drug
毒药会残留在你们的脑组织里
will stay in your brain tissue post-mortem.
因为在英国  我是唯一的
Since I'm the only man in Britain
拥有专门技术生产和管理
who possesses the expertise to process and administer
这非致命药剂的人
a non-lethal dose,
我会被怀疑的
I would fall under suspicion.
我必须毁掉这个证据
This evidence I must destroy.
很不幸  但有时科学就要有所牺牲
It is unfortunate, but sometimes science requires sacrifice.
别担心  我动手很快
Don't worry. I will be quick.
就来了
Coming.
对不起
I'm sorry.
为所有的事情
For everything.
都是我的错  与你无关
It's my fault, not yours.
我太固执了  太沉迷于
I've been stubborn and so obsessed
追求自己的梦想  从没花时间
with chasing my own dreams I never even took the time
了解你的梦想  现在我了解了
to understand yours, and I do.
我意识到  你不需要我的保护
But I now realize you don't require my protection.
你不需要遵照世俗
And you are in no need of keeping.
那么  如果…如果可以
So, if... if you could,
让我接着爱你
just let me love you instead.
晚安  Murray小姐
Good evening, Miss Murray.
Jonathan!
你忘了最重要的事
You've forgotten the most important thing.
是什么？
What?
娶我
Marry me.
做我的丈夫  我做你的妻子
Be my husband, and I will be your wife.
我曾经很多次的想向你求婚
I wanted to ask you so many times.
我甚至买了一枚戒指
I even bought a ring.
等下
Wait.
我可以么？
May I?
我今天碰到的最奇怪的事
The oddest thing happened to me today.
是吗  先生  就一件？
Really, sir? Just one?
我表演了一番  让他人得到的欢乐
I performed an act which brought great joy
比我的快乐还要多
to someone other than myself.
谁？
Whom?
Harker  还有 Mina Murray.
Harker, Mina Murray.
那您到底做了什么？
What exactly did you do?
我引导他们回到彼此身边
I guided the one back to the other.
现在看来  他们会结婚
By the looks of it, they'll be wed.
那是件好事
A good deed then.
是的
Yes.
我应该惊骇
I should be horrified.
但说实话  我并不反感这感觉
But in truth I can't say I dislike this feeling.
- 但是…  - 但是
- And yet... - And yet.
让你的雇员和Murray小姐在一起
Keeping your employee and Miss Murray together
就是把她留在您的生活轨道内
keeps her in your orbit.
就像重力  恰到好处  不远不近
Like gravity. Close but not too close.
可让她离去也许更明智
When it might be wiser to let her go.
有时候过于聪明对你没好处
Sometimes you're too smart for your own good.
就像一个磨盘挂在我脖子上  是个负担
It's like a millstone around my neck.
那天早上
On that first morning
他们造就了我
when they made me what I am,
阳光灼烧我的皮肤
the sunlight burned my skin.
不知何情  不晓何故
I don't know how or why,
但我就知道我不一样了
but I knew I would never be the same.
你做了什么？
What did you do?
扯掉了混蛋牧师的喉咙
Ripped out the throat of the bastard priest.
所以  总的来说  不是个糟糕的早晨
So not a bad morning, all things considered.
我经历过更糟糕的
I've had worse.
怎么会这样？
How can this be?
我不知道
I don't know.
从未有过
It's unprecedented.
反向追踪…之前从未发生过
To track the trackers... It has never been done before.
- 这是场灾难  - 哦  还有更糟的
- It's a disaster. - Oh, it's worse than that.
这是我在找的那个吸血鬼干的
This is the work of the vampire that I seek.
由于先知死了
Now that the seers are dead,
他能够更容易的吸引来他的族类
he will much more easily attract others of his kind.
可恶
An abomination.
很快伦敦就会挤满了这些毒物
Soon London will be crawling with the vermin.
Stephen.
Daniel!
哦  我的孩子！
Oh, my boy!
Grayson.
Grayson!